[{"answer": "Good afternoon.  Are you ready to check out?  Did you find everything OK", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Yes, thank you", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Good afternoon.  Are you ready to check out?  Did you find everything OK", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Would you like paper or plastic", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Yes, thank you", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Plastic please", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Would you like paper or plastic", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Do you have any coupons or a savings card with us", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Plastic please", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Yes, here is my savings card", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Do you have any coupons or a savings card with us", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " OK.  Youre total is $56.75.  Will you be paying with cash, check, credit, or debit", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Yes, here is my savings card", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Credit", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " OK.  Youre total is $56.75.  Will you be paying with cash, check, credit, or debit", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " OK, please swipe your card", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Credit", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " OK, please swipe your card", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " OK.  Here is your receipt.  You saved $4.43 with your savings card today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 26, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Great", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 27, "question": " OK.  Here is your receipt.  You saved $4.43 with your savings card today", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Would you like help carrying your groceries out to your car", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Great", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " No, thanks.  I got it", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Would you like help carrying your groceries out to your car", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Well, have a nice day", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 30, "question": " No, thanks.  I got it", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " You too", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well, have a nice day", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Do you need help with anything", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " You too", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " No thank you.  Im just browsing", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Do you need help with anything", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " OK.  Let me know if I can help you find anything.  Also, just to let yo", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 39, "question": " No thank you.  Im just browsing", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 44, "question": " OK.  Let me know if I can help you find anything.  Also, just to let yo", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Excuse me, maam.  Can I try these jeans on", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Sure, the fitting room is just over here", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Excuse me, maam.  Can I try these jeans on", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Did they fit", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Sure, the fitting room is just over here", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Yes, theyre a little tight but I think theyll be OK.  Are these jeans included i", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Did they fit", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Yes, those jeans are part of the sale.  Theyd be 35% off today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Yes, theyre a little tight but I think theyll be OK.  Are these jeans included i", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " OK, I guess Ill get them then", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Yes, those jeans are part of the sale.  Theyd be 35% off today", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " OK, I can ring you up right here.  Will that be all for you today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": " OK, I guess Ill get them then", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Yes thanks.  Do you take credit cards", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 62, "question": " OK, I can ring you up right here.  Will that be all for you today", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " We do.  Would you like to save an extra 10% by opening up our stor", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Yes thanks.  Do you take credit cards", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " No thank you.  Not today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 67, "question": " We do.  Would you like to save an extra 10% by opening up our stor", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " OK.  No problem.  Here you are.  Your receipt is in the bag.  Have ", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 68, "question": " No thank you.  Not today", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 72, "question": " OK.  No problem.  Here you are.  Your receipt is in the bag.  Have ", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Do you need help finding anything", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Yes, Im looking for an electric pencil sharpener", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Do you need help finding anything", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " We have some on aisle four.  Please follow me", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Yes, Im looking for an electric pencil sharpener", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 81, "question": " We have some on aisle four.  Please follow me", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Here they are.  Did you need anything else today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 82, "question": " OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " No, thats it", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Here they are.  Did you need anything else today", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " OK.  The registers are up front when youre ready to check out", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 84, "question": " No, thats it", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you for your help", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 85, "question": " OK.  The registers are up front when youre ready to check out", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Youre welcome", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 86, "question": " OK.  Thank you for your help", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Good morning.  Are you purchasing these books today", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Youre welcome", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " No, actually Im returning them.  I bought them last week for a friend, bu", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Good morning.  Are you purchasing these books today", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " OK, can I see your receipt please", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 100, "question": " No, actually Im returning them.  I bought them last week for a friend, bu", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " My receipt?  Sorry, I dont have it.  I think I threw it away", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 101, "question": " OK, can I see your receipt please", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Im sorry maam, but we can only accept returns if you have a receip", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 102, "question": " My receipt?  Sorry, I dont have it.  I think I threw it away", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " But I bought them here last week", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 106, "question": " Im sorry maam, but we can only accept returns if you have a receip", "qSentId": 105},{"answer": " Im sorry about that maam.  We can give you store credit without th", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 107, "question": " But I bought them here last week", "qSentId": 106},{"answer": " OK.  I guess Ill take the store credit", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 111, "question": " Im sorry about that maam.  We can give you store credit without th", "qSentId": 110},{"answer": " Sure.  So here is your gift card with a total of $24.56 in store credit", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 112, "question": " OK.  I guess Ill take the store credit", "qSentId": 111},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 113, "question": " Sure.  So here is your gift card with a total of $24.56 in store credit", "qSentId": 112},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Remember to keep your receipt for all purchases i", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 114, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 113},{"answer": " I will.  Bye", "docId": "11-03", "aSentId": 118, "question": " Youre welcome.  Remember to keep your receipt for all purchases i", "qSentId": 117}]
